Geneva, International Interpol Bureau
Detective Dubois said, "Look at this!"
What is it, François?
The victim was found near
the Rhône river — cost: €5,000.
Inspector, we need your help
with this case.
"Of course. What do we know
so far?" he replied.
¿Dónde está el informe médico?
Dr. García, aquí está el análisis.
¡Increíble! La víctima murió
hace más de 24 horas.
Herr Müller, können Sie
das bestätigen?
Ja, natürlich. Die Beweise
sind eindeutig.
INTERROGATION ROOM
Please tell us what you saw
that night.
I saw a yellow car near
the old boat — approximately 200 meters.
Était-il seul dans la voiture?
Non, il y avait une femme
à côté de lui.
¿Puede describirla más detalladamente?
Tenía el cabello rubio
y llevaba un abrigo rojo.
Das passt zur Beschreibung
der Verdächtigen!
Wir müssen sie sofort finden.
FORENSIC LABORATORY
We found fingerprints
on the weapon.
Excellent work! Are they
in our database?
Les empreintes correspondent
à Céline Beaumont.
C'est elle! La suspecte
que nous cherchions!
¿Ya tienen una orden de detención?
Sí, el juez la firmó
hace una hora.
Ausgezeichnet! Schicken Sie
alle verfügbaren Einheiten.
Diese Frau darf nicht
entkommen.
END OF TRANSMISSION