[thunder rumbling]
[eerie music playing]
[engine revving] [tires screeching]
-(GROANS)
-You okay?
[glass shatters] What was that?
DISPATCHER (over radio): Unit 5, respond
[in Spanish] Buenos días
-[clears throat]
-As I was saying...
(PHONE RINGING)
(DOOR KNOCKING)
[WOMAN ON TV] Today's forecast shows...
♪♪ (upbeat jazz playing)
[speaking indistinctly]
-(GASPS) Oh my God!
-(SCREAMS)
[ANNOUNCER] And the winner is...
(wind howling)
It's so cold
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
-Run!
-I'm trying!
[boy] She sleepwalks sometimes
since our parents died.
-Nobody, that's who. [chuckles]
-["My Favourite Game" playing on stereo]
-First person speaking
-Second person responds
-Third person adds comment